



GetX Dart

javascript

Expo

Team Work

Git

Firebase

Java

Redux

Hooks

Clean Architecture

Google Maps API

Android Native

Build Android & iOS



LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency



CERTIFICATES

Dasar-dasar Mobile Programming Android untuk Pemula

Skill Academy By Ruang Guru

04/2022

UX Designer Digital Product

Development

Skill Academy By Ruang Guru 04/2022

Artificial Intelligence untuk Bisnis

Skill Academy By Ruang Guru 04/2022

AGUS RAKHMADI MIDO

Mobile Developer (Flutter and React Native)

Greetings, I'm Mido, an experienced mobile developer specializing in crafting exceptional mobile applications. Starting with Java, I developed polished applications. Subsequently, I expanded my skill set to include JavaScript, and later, Dart to create engaging Android and iOS apps using Flutter and React Native. Motivated by the pursuit of excellence, I am dedicated to continuously refining and advancing my skills in delivering innovative and reliable mobile solutions.

midosaurus

<u>agusrahmadimido</u>@gmail.com

midoandev midoandev

in agusrahmadimido

(c) <u>agusrahmadimido</u>

Yogyakarta, Indonesia



WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer

Digital Sekuriti Indonesia

02/2022 - Present

Yogyakarta

Digital Sekuriti Indonesia is technology platform driven leveraging Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning.

Tasks

- As a programmer working especially in the mobile development section using Flutter and React Native.
- Work with the team in assisting in providing solutions in the creation of application algorithms
- Evaluate the code that co-workers have completed

Android Developer

Imkom Academy

02/2018 - 02/2022

Yogyakarta

Imkom Academy is the place for courses about technology

Tasks

- Working on several cross-platform application projects that have been published on Playstore and AppStore
- I also work as a teacher in the Java programming language, especially Androidbased mobile apps



EDUCATION

Master in Information Technology

University of Technology Yogyakarta

09/2018 - 12/2021

Yogyakarta

Computer Engineering

University of Technology Yogyakarta

07/2014 - 04/2018

Yogyakarta